loginradius.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy | LoginRadius

#### Introduction

We respect your privacy, and want to ensure the best experience while interacting with LoginRadius Inc (“LoginRadius”, “we” or “us”), while using our services (“LoginRadius Services”, “LoginRadius API” or “LoginRadius Platform” or “LoginRadius Products”), or browsing our website www.loginradius.com (“Website”, or “LoginRadius Website”), including the internal dashboard provided to our Customers. LoginRadius’ Services are deployed on our Customers’ web or mobile applications (“Customer Web Applications” or “Customer Websites”) and is used by our Customers’ online users (“End-Users”).

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose the Personal and non-Personal Information of our customers and End-Users (as defined below) on the LoginRadius Website and through LoginRadius’ Services.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated to and is subject to the LoginRadius Terms of Use, and any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the meaning provided in our Terms of Use. By using LoginRadius’ Website or Services, you consent to the use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Operation of LoginRadius Website

The LoginRadius website has three key purposes : i) Providing information on our products, services, and on technical support and resources, ii) as a key channel of communication, and iii) providing access to the LoginRadius Dashboard to let our Customers manage their LoginRadius account and configurations. During the operation of the Website, we may collect your personal information via various channels such as contact forms, live chats, account creation, etc.

#### Operation of LoginRadius Services

LoginRadius Services are delivered to our Customers and their End-Users users via our API, SDK, and/or plugins on our Customers’ web applications. In order to provide these services, LoginRadius may collect some Personal and Non-Personal Information of the End-Users on behalf of our Customers. The collected information is owned by that LoginRadius Customer and will be used as per this Privacy Policy, as well as per our Customer’s privacy policy.

#### Information We Collect

We aim to collect and use such information as is required to enable us to manage our Customer accounts, provide LoginRadius Services, maintain our Customer/visitor lists, respond to inquiries or provide feedback, for identification and authentication purposes, and for service improvements. We will only use your Personal Information for the purposes for which they were collected.

Two types of information may be collected through the Website and our Services: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. This Privacy Policy does not extend to the collection, use, or disclosure of the following information which is currently not limited by applicable privacy laws: (a) information that is publicly available, such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, and electronic addresses when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; or (b) Non-Personal Information (as defined further below).

" _Personal Information_ " is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, credit card information, birth date, and gender. At the time of collection, we will clearly identify the information being collected and the purposes for which it will be used. It is always the Customer’s choice whether or not to provide Personal Information, but if the Customer chooses not to provide certain requested Personal Information, in some instances the Customer may not be able to register to use the Website, or be able to access and use the Website at all. 

In other instances, the Customers’ choice not to provide certain Personal Information may mean that the Customer will not be able to use certain features of the Website or the Service. We may collect Personal Information through registration processes, communications with the Customer, information downloads, service use, user support, and surveys.

" _Non-Personal Information_ " is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access the Website, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used by visitors to the website. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors, what pages users access or visit, and average time spent on the Website is not considered Personal Information.

Such Non-Personal Information may be collected by LoginRadius in the course of operating the Website. For example, our web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information that is provided through your browser or stored in a cookie when you choose to visit the Website.

#### How We Use the Information that We Collect

We may use the information (Personal as well as Non-Personal) in the following ways:

  1. We will use your email address to contact you about important information or notices about LoginRadius or to respond to your queries. We may display your name, email address, and other information within your LoginRadius account as well as other sections of the website. It will only be viewable to you.
  2. We may use non-personally identifiable information to statistically analyze our web and business performances. This helps us to enhance your experience with our services.
  3. If you write a testimonial for us and give us consent to publish it, we may display your name, title, and company on our testimonial section. We never disclose or share any information which identifies you personally with any third party. (Please see below disclosure for further details.)
  4. End-User information is used to deliver services to our Customers, provide analytics, and other services. Our Customers own that information.

#### When We Disclose Information

LoginRadius does not share, sell, or rent your information to any third party website or company. We may require disclosing your personal information to respond to legal requirements, to enforce our policies, to respond to claims that you or use of service by you violates another's rights, or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.

#### Security

Any personal data you provide us is securely stored in a database which only a few authorized employees can access. The server holding your personal data is protected against unauthorized physical as well as electronic access. These measures include an electronic firewall and various other protection measures that involve virus scanning, installation of security patches, vulnerability testing, backup, recovery planning, employee training, security audits, and other steps designed to constantly improve the data protection procedures. The server is not directly connected to the internet and data is therefore available only to authorized computers. However, LoginRadius cannot assure full security as it is not possible to make a system 100% secure in practice.

#### EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield

LoginRadius complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. LoginRadius has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. This also applies to the personal information gathered from our prospect and current employees who are citizens of European Union and Switzerland. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, LoginRadius commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should direct any inquiries or complaints concerning our Privacy Shield compliance to legal@loginradius.com. LoginRadius will respond within 45 days. If we fail to respond within that time, or if our response does not address your concern, you may contact the International Centre for Dispute Resolution, the international division of the American Arbitration Association (ICDR/AAA), which provides an independent third-party dispute resolution body based in the United States, [here](https://go.adr.org/privacyshield.html). ICDR/AAA has committed to respond to complaints and to provide appropriate recourse at no cost to you.

LoginRadius responsibility includes processing of received personal data, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and transfer it to designated third party agent acting on our behalf. LoginRadius is compliant with the Privacy Shield Principles for transfer of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including liability provision for the same. Personal data received or transferred pursuant to privacy shield frameworks, LoginRadius will abide by the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

For complaints from EU and Swiss data subjects that cannot be resolved with LoginRadius directly, LoginRadius has committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC). If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs and the Swiss FDPIC for more information or to file a complaint.

In case of lawful requests by public authorities or law enforcement or national security, LoginRadius may disclose personal data as required. You can invoke binding arbitration as outlined on [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>] if other dispute resolution procedures are exhausted.

#### Your Rights

We offer you choices regarding the data collection, use, and sharing of your personal information. We will periodically send you newsletters and emails that directly promote the use of our site or the purchase of our services. When you receive newsletters from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications and you will have the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email or by contacting us directly (using the contact information below). Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our privacy policy or system alert/billing messages.

You can ask us to correct and, where relevant, erase your information. Please note that certain Personal Information may need to be retained by LoginRadius for a period of time following cancellation of your account. This is necessary for legitimate business purposes and required or authorized by applicable law. As mentioned above you have a right to change your Personal Information at any time by logging into your LoginRadius dashboard or by sending us an email.

#### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

#### Online Advertising

We have active advertising campaigns from third parties collecting cookies from our web users. This information is used for conversion and remarketing purposes.

You should be informed of the Following:

  * LoginRadius has implemented and uses Display Advertising.
  * Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.
  * LoginRadius uses Remarketing with a number of third-party advertising solutions.
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet.
  * LoginRadius and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to your website.

#### Business Relationships with Social ID Providers

LoginRadius may have business relations (or partnerships) with some social ID providers such as Google, Facebook, Amazon, etc. However, we are not responsible for the terms of use and privacy policies for any of these social ID providers. Please visit their websites for more information about their privacy policies and terms of use.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy by posting a new version on our website. If we make any material changes, we will notify Customers by providing notices via email or through a notification in the LoginRadius Dashboard used to access your LoginRadius account. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.

#### Contact and Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy,  
please contact our email at: [privacy@loginradius.com](mailto:privacy@loginradius.com)

#### Additional Terms of Service

If you are a customer of LoginRadius, your use of the LoginRadius Service is subject to LoginRadius Terms of Service, available at [www.loginradius.com/terms](https://www.loginradius.com/terms/)

Address: General Counsel,  
c/o LoginRadius Inc.  
500 - 1281 W Georgia Street  
Vancouver BC  
Canada V6E 3J7
